[
    {
        "number": "1",
        "question": "1. I can fall off a building and live, but in water I will die. What am I?",
        "answer": "paper"
    },    
    {
        "number": "2",
        "question": "2. I am a vegetable that bugs stay away from. What am I?",
        "answer": "squash"
    },
    {
        "number": "3",
        "question": "3. I have hundreds of legs but I can only lean; You make me feel dirty so you feel clean. What am I?",
        "answer": "broom"
    },
    {
        "number": "4",
        "question": "4. I can be cracked, made, told, and played. What am I?",
        "answer": "joke"
    },
    {
        "number": "5",
        "question": "5. I am gentle enough to soothe your skin, light enough to fly in the sky, strong enough to crack rocks. What am I?",
        "answer": "water"
    },
    {
        "number": "6",
        "question": "6. The more you take of me, the more you leave behind. What am I?",
        "answer": "footstep"
    },
    {
        "number": "7",
        "question": "7. I shrink smaller every time I take a bath. What am I?",
        "answer": "soap"
    },
    {
        "number": "8",
        "question": "8. I have a face but no eyes, hands but no arms. What am I?",
        "answer": "clock"
    },  
    {
        "number": "9",
        "question": "9. The more you take away from me, the bigger I shall get. What am I?",
        "answer": "hole"
    },  
    {
        "number": "10",
        "question": "10. I jump when I walk and sit when I stand. What am I?",
        "answer": "kangaroo"
    },  
    {
        "number": "11",
        "question": "11. You can catch me but cannot throw me. What am I?",
        "answer": "cold"
    },  
    {
        "number": "12",
        "question": "12. I start with 'T', ends with 'T', and within me is 'T'. What am I?",
        "answer": "teapot"
    },  
    {
        "number": "13",
        "question": "13. Soft, hairy, from door to door. I am the pet that always stays on the floor. What am I?",
        "answer": "carpet"
    }, 
    {
        "number": "14",
        "question": "14. I must be broken before you can use me. What am I?",
        "answer": "egg"
    },
    {
        "number": "15",
        "question": "15. I go up when the rain comes down. What am I?",
        "answer": "umbrella"
    }  
]